export const questions = [
  {
    "answer": "Bishop",
    "question": "Which chess piece can only move diagonally?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Colony",
    "question": "What is a community of ants called?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Diamond",
    "question": "What’s the hardest rock?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Metal key",
    "question": "What object did Ben Franklin attach to the end of a kite string to prove that lightning is electricity?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Mirror",
    "question": "What object is said to bring bad luck if it is broken?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Stag",
    "question": "What is Harry Potter’s Patronus?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "A. A. Milne",
    "question": "Which author wrote the ‘Winnie-the-Pooh’ books?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Ahi",
    "question": "What is the Hawaiian name for yellowfin tuna?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Alabama",
    "question": "In what American state is it illegal to dress up like a priest or a nun?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Alicia Silverstone",
    "question": "Who played Cher Horowitz in the movie “Clueless”?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Allies and Axis",
    "question": "What were the two sides in World War II known as?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Almonds",
    "question": "Which nuts are used to make marzipan?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Aluminium",
    "question": "What is the most abundant metal in the Earth’s crust?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Amman",
    "question": "What is the name of Jordan’s capital city?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Amsterdam",
    "question": "In which city was Anne Frank’s hiding place?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "An aglet",
    "question": "What is the tiny piece at the end of a shoelace called?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "An alarm clock",
    "question": "What did the Crocodile swallow in Peter Pan?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Antarctica",
    "question": "What is the driest continent?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Aorta",
    "question": "What is the biggest artery in the human body?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Apple Trees",
    "question": "\"American pioneer, John Chapman, was famous for planting which kind of tree?\""
  },
  {
    "answer": "Apple",
    "question": "Which fruit floats because 25% of its volume is air?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Arizona and Hawaii",
    "question": "Which two U.S. states don’t observe Daylight Saving Time?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Asia",
    "question": "Nepal is located on which continent?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Australia",
    "question": "Canberra is the capital city of which country?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Australia",
    "question": "Saudi Arabia imports camels from what country?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Australia",
    "question": "What country has the world’s most ancient forest?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Bakery",
    "question": "What type of business did Annie have that failed in “Bridesmaids”?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Baklava",
    "question": "What do you call filo pastry stuffed with chopped nuts and honey or syrup?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Barbara Streisand ",
    "question": "What celebrity has their dog cloned– twice?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Barcelona",
    "question": "The Eiffel Tower was originally intended for what city?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Bavarian Motor Works",
    "question": "What does BMW stand for (in English)?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Bedrock",
    "question": "What is the name of the prehistoric town in which The Flinstones live?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Berlin",
    "question": "In which city did Hitler commit suicide?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Berlin",
    "question": "Ludwig Van Beethoven was born in 1770 in which city?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Bill Clinton",
    "question": "What US president put a Twinkie in the country’s millennium time capsule?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Billie Jean King",
    "question": "Who was Sports Illustrated’s first female sportsperson of the year?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Black Hole",
    "question": "What has a gravitational pull so strong that even light cannot escape it?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Black",
    "question": "Apple’s CEO Steve Jobs was known for wearing what color turtleneck?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Black",
    "question": "What color is a polar bear’s skin?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Blue Ivy Carter",
    "question": "Who is the youngest person ever to appear on a Billboard chart?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Boxing Day",
    "question": "\"In the United Kingdom, what is the day after Christmas known as?\""
  },
  {
    "answer": "Brass",
    "question": "The tuba is the largest member of which musical family?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Brazil",
    "question": "Which country produces the most coffee in the world?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Brown",
    "question": "What color eyes do most humans have?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Brown",
    "question": "What is the rarest M&M color?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Buckingham Palace",
    "question": "What’s the most expensive home in the world?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Budweiser",
    "question": "What American beer has been long promoted as the “King of Beers”?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Canada and the USA",
    "question": "Which two countries share the longest international border?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Canada",
    "question": "“Cirque du Soleil” started in what country?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Cancer",
    "question": "Which horoscope sign has a crab?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Carbon Dioxide",
    "question": "What gas makes soda bubbly?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Chickpea",
    "question": "What is the main ingredient in a falafel?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "China",
    "question": "What country produced the most strawberries in 2016?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Christina Aguilera",
    "question": "Which female singer discovered a ‘Genie in a Bottle’ in 1999?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Christmas Tree Farm",
    "question": "Taylor Swift grew up on what type of farm?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Classical",
    "question": "What type of music has been shown to help plants grow better and faster?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "College of Cardinals",
    "question": "What is the name of the group of men who elect a Pope?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Concave",
    "question": "What type of lens has a thin middle and makes objects appear smaller?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Cranberry and lime",
    "question": "What are the two fruit juices in a cosmopolitan?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Cricket",
    "question": "Which insect can indicate the air temperature?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "David Bowie",
    "question": "Who created the alien rock superstar Ziggy Stardust?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "De Klerk",
    "question": "Which President of South Africa ordered Nelson Mandela’s release from prison?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Dead Sea",
    "question": "Which sea is located in Israel and Jordan?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Delaware ",
    "question": "What was the first state?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Detroit",
    "question": "Where did rap superstar Eminem grow up?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Earthquakes",
    "question": "What does a seismologist study?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Eels",
    "question": "\"In medieval England, what was used as currency, specifically for rental agreements?\""
  },
  {
    "answer": "Elton John",
    "question": "Who wrote songs for The Lion King?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Ethiopia ",
    "question": "Which African country was formerly known as Abyssinia?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "E",
    "question": "What is the most common letter in the English alphabet?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "\"Five: Dopey, Grumpy, Sneezy, Sleepy, Happy\"",
    "question": "How many of Snow White’s seven dwarfs have names ending in the letter Y?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Five",
    "question": "How many eyes does a bee have?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Flamingos",
    "question": "A flamboyance is a group of what animals?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Fort Knox",
    "question": "\"Where were the Declaration of Independence, the Constitution, and the Bill of Rights stored during World War II?\""
  },
  {
    "answer": "France",
    "question": "The Statue of Liberty was given to the US by which country?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Free At Last",
    "question": "What 3-word phrase is written on Martin Luther King’s gravestone?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Fulgencio Batista",
    "question": "Who preceded Fidel Castro as the political leader of Cuba?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Garbanzo",
    "question": "\"As what type of beans are chickpeas, also known as?\""
  },
  {
    "answer": "George",
    "question": "What was Babe Ruth’s first name?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Gianni Versace",
    "question": "Which fashion designer was shot dead in the summer of 1997?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Giraffe",
    "question": "Which mammal has no vocal cords?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Glass",
    "question": "Complete the title of a 1979 number one by Blondie – ‘Heart of…’"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Good Will Hunting",
    "question": "Robin Williams won a best supporting actor Oscar for what film?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Greenland",
    "question": "What is the world’s biggest island?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Green",
    "question": "What color is Absinthe?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Gwen Stefani",
    "question": "\"Kingston, Zuma, and Apollo are the sons of which American female pop star?\""
  },
  {
    "answer": "HMS Beagle",
    "question": "\"On which ship did Charles Darwin make his famous expedition, which led to his evolution theory?\""
  },
  {
    "answer": "Haiti",
    "question": "Port-au-Prince is the capital of which country?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Hamlet",
    "question": "Which of Shakespeare’s plays is the longest?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Hawaii",
    "question": "\"Which name are the Sandwich Islands, better known as?\""
  },
  {
    "answer": "Health of newborns",
    "question": "An Apgar score is given to what?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Holy Water",
    "question": "What did the first vending machine dispense?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Honeybee",
    "question": "The male of what species testicles explode on mating and then dies?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Hope",
    "question": "A book by Barack Obama is titled “The Audacity of” what?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Hydrogen",
    "question": "What is the first element on the Periodic Table?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Hydrogen",
    "question": "What is the most abundant element in the universe?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "In The Throat",
    "question": "Where is the uvula located?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Ireland",
    "question": "In what country did carving jack o’ lanterns originate?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Ireland",
    "question": "What country is the band “The Cranberries” from?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Italy",
    "question": "Galileo was the citizen of which country?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Japan",
    "question": "What country has the most vending machines per capita?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Jaws",
    "question": "“You’re gonna need a bigger boat” originated in what movie?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Jenny",
    "question": "\"If a male donkey is a jack, what is the female called?\""
  },
  {
    "answer": "Jesse Eisenberg",
    "question": "Who performs the character of Mark Zuckerberg in the movie “The Social Network”?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Joan of Arc",
    "question": "Which young girl helped drive the English from French soil in the 15th century?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Johnny Depp",
    "question": "What major movie actor’s first role was in “A Nightmare On Elm Street”?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Jupiter",
    "question": "What is the largest planet in our solar system?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Justin Rolland",
    "question": "Who voices Morty in the series “Rick and Morty”?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Kate Winslet",
    "question": "Which actress keeps her Oscar in her bathroom so guests can hold it and make speeches in the mirror shame-free?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Kentucky",
    "question": "Which US state has the longest cave system in the world?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Keratin",
    "question": "What substance are nails made out of?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Kindergarten Teacher",
    "question": "\"On the television show “How I Met Your Mother,” what is Lily’s occupation?\""
  },
  {
    "answer": "Knee cap",
    "question": "Which bone are babies born without?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Koalas",
    "question": "\"Chimpanzees and gorillas have human-like fingerprints, and so do what other non-human animals?\""
  },
  {
    "answer": "Komodo dragon",
    "question": "What is the largest lizard?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Kroger Co.",
    "question": "What is the biggest supermarket chain in the U.S.?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Lady Gaga",
    "question": "Which singer’s real name is Stefani Joanne Angelina Germanotta?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Larry",
    "question": "What is the Twitter bird’s official?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "League of Nations",
    "question": "What was the predecessor to the United Nations?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Led Zeppelin",
    "question": "What was the name of the rock band formed by Jimmy Page?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Leonardo da Vinci",
    "question": "Who invented scissors?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Lourve",
    "question": "The Da Vinci Code opens with a murder in which famous museum?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Love",
    "question": "\"In ancient Greece, throwing an apple at someone was a declaration of what?\""
  },
  {
    "answer": "Madagascar",
    "question": "Which country is the largest producer of vanilla?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Maine",
    "question": "What is the only state that borders just one other state?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Margaret Thatcher",
    "question": "Who was the first female Prime Minister of Great Britain?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Marie Curie",
    "question": "Who was the first woman to win a Nobel Prize (1903)?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Marty McFly",
    "question": "What character did Michael J. Fox play in ‘Back to the Future’?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Matt Groening",
    "question": "Who created the animated series “Futurama”?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Maya Angelou",
    "question": "I Know Why the Caged Bird Sings’ is an autobiography about the early years of what inspirational African-American writer and poet?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Mediterranean Sea",
    "question": "Europe is separated from Africa by which sea?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Mercury",
    "question": "What is the only metal that is a liquid at normal atmospheric pressure and temperature?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Meryl Streep",
    "question": "What actress won her first Oscar for “Kramer vs. Kramer”?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Mexico",
    "question": "Which country was the Caesar salad invented in?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Moby Dick",
    "question": "What book starts with the line “Call me Ishmael.”?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Mona Lisa",
    "question": "What is the painting ‘La Gioconda’ more usually known as?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Morocco",
    "question": "Which country has a red flag with a star in the middle?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Mr. Potato Head",
    "question": "What was the first toy to be advertised on television?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Muhammed Ali",
    "question": "Who was said to “float like a butterfly and sting like a bee”?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Mussolini",
    "question": "Which Italian fascist leader was known as ‘Il Duce’?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Nestle",
    "question": "What company makes the Butterfinger bar?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "New England Patriots",
    "question": "Which NFL team holds the record for the most Super Bowl appearances?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "New Jersey",
    "question": "Which U.S. state has “Garden State” as its nickname?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "New York City",
    "question": "What’s the most populous city in the United States?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Norma Jeane",
    "question": "What is the real first name of Marilyn Monroe?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "North America",
    "question": "Blueberries are native to which continent?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "O negative",
    "question": "What blood type qualifies as a universal donor?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Oak Tree",
    "question": "What grows from an acorn?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "P. Diddy",
    "question": "Which name is rapper Sean Combs better known by?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Pablo Picasso",
    "question": "Which artist painted “Guernica”?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Paella",
    "question": "What is the national dish of Spain?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Pakistan",
    "question": "Islamabad is the capital of which country?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Pandora",
    "question": "\"According to Greek mythology, who was the first woman on earth?\""
  },
  {
    "answer": "Parent Trap",
    "question": "Which 1998 Disney film was Lindsay Lohan’s film debut?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Paris",
    "question": "In what city did Princess Diana suffer her fatal car crash?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Paris",
    "question": "In which European city would you find Orly airport?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Paris",
    "question": "In which city is Jim Morrison buried?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Penguins",
    "question": "The video game “Happy Feet” features what animals?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Phalanges",
    "question": "What are the bones in the fingers called?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Philadelphia",
    "question": "Which US city is known as the City of Brotherly Love?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Pigeon",
    "question": "Squab is a name given to the young of which bird?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Pigs",
    "question": "What animal is constitutionally protected in Florida?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Pimento",
    "question": "What is allspice alternatively known as?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Pineapple Express",
    "question": "Which 2008 comedy had the tagline “Put this in your pipe and smoke it”?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Pineapple",
    "question": "Which type of fruit juice did Dole sell first?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Pinocchio",
    "question": "Which Disney film features the song ‘When You Wish Upon a Star’?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Plants",
    "question": "Botany is the scientific study of what?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Pocahontas",
    "question": "What was the first Disney animated film based on the life of a real person?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Podrick Payne",
    "question": "Which character becomes Brienne’s squire in season 4 of “Game of Thrones”?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Poland",
    "question": "\"What country is bordered by Germany, the Czech Republic, Slovakia, and Ukraine?\""
  },
  {
    "answer": "Poland",
    "question": "Which country did bagels originate from?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Prius",
    "question": "What was Toyota’s first popular hybrid car called?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Private",
    "question": "What is the lowest army rank of a US soldier?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Proton",
    "question": "What particle in an atom has a positive charge?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Prunes",
    "question": "What is the common name for dried plums?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Purple",
    "question": "\"The traditional Wimbledon colors are green, and what?\""
  },
  {
    "answer": "Queen Of The Highway",
    "question": "Which Doors song is about Jim Morrison’s relationship with Pamela Courson?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Rand",
    "question": "What currency is used in South Africa?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Red meat",
    "question": "A tick bite can make you allergic to what food?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Red",
    "question": "What color dresses do Chinese women traditionally wear on their wedding day?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Reese’s Pieces",
    "question": "What candy was used to lure E.T. in the 1982 movie “E.T.: The Extra-Terrestrial”?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Restricted",
    "question": "What does the “R” stand for on the rating of a movie?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Rice",
    "question": "What is Japanese sake made from?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Richard Nixon",
    "question": "Who was the only US President to resign?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Rome",
    "question": "\"On every continent, there is a city named what?\""
  },
  {
    "answer": "Rosh Hashanah",
    "question": "What is the Jewish New Year called?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Rubber",
    "question": "What is an ice hockey puck made from?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Saturn and Jupiter",
    "question": "What planets literally rain diamonds?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Seattle",
    "question": "What city did Starbucks open its first store in 1971?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Secretariat",
    "question": "What famous horse won the Triple Crown in 1973?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Seven",
    "question": "How many red stripes are there on the American flag?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Sirius",
    "question": "What’s the brightest star in the sky?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Six",
    "question": "\"When Michael Jordan played for the Chicago Bulls, how many NBA Championships did he win?\""
  },
  {
    "answer": "Spice Girls",
    "question": "Which British girl group had a member by the name of Mel B?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Spiciness",
    "question": "What does a Scoville unit measure?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Squirrels ",
    "question": "Power outages in the US are mostly caused by what?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Stapler",
    "question": "What object of Dwight’s did Jim put in Jell-O on the TV show “The Office”?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Strawberry",
    "question": "What is the only fruit that has its seeds on the outside?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Sugar",
    "question": "What is “jaggery” used in Indian cooking?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Surrealism",
    "question": "Which art movement is Salvador Dali associated with?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Switzerland",
    "question": "Which country consumes the most chocolate per capita?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Talc",
    "question": "What is the softest mineral in the world?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Tennis Elbow",
    "question": "Lateral Epicondylitis is a condition commonly known by what name?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Thailand",
    "question": "Which country is known as the Land of White Elephant?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Tootsie Rolls",
    "question": "What candy ran the promotion for baseball’s one-millionth run?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Toronto",
    "question": "What is the most populous city in Canada?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Toxic",
    "question": "In which of Britney’s video does she appear as a stewardess?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Tulips",
    "question": "Which kind of bulbs were once exchanged as a form of currency?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Twenty-four",
    "question": "How many ribs are in a human body?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Umbrellas",
    "question": "Rihanna banned fans from bringing what items to her U.K. concerts in 2008?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "University of Chicago",
    "question": "Where did Barack Obama teach constitutional law?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Uruguay",
    "question": "What country won the very first FIFA World Cup in 1930?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Vatican City",
    "question": "What is the smallest country in the world?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Venus",
    "question": "Which planet is the hottest in the solar system?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Vermeer",
    "question": "Which Dutch artist painted “Girl with a Pearl Earring”?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Vitamin A",
    "question": "Carrots are a good source of which vitamin?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Vitamin D",
    "question": "What vitamin does the sun’s ultraviolet rays help the skin produce?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Volcanos",
    "question": "\"Fissures, vents, and plugs are all associated with which geological feature?\""
  },
  {
    "answer": "Wax",
    "question": "Which is the main substance used to make a crayon?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "World War 1",
    "question": "Tanks were used in battle for the first time in which conflict?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "World Wide Web",
    "question": "\"In a website browser address bar, what does “www” stand for?\""
  },
  {
    "answer": "Wrench",
    "question": "\"The Candlestick, Lead Pipe, Knife, Revolver, Rope, and what else are the six weapons in a standard game of Clue?\""
  },
  {
    "answer": "Wrestling",
    "question": "Tom Cruise considered pursuing a career in what sport before being injured?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Yellow",
    "question": "What color jersey is worn by the winners of each stage of the Tour De France?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Zero",
    "question": "How many children does Oprah Winfrey have?"
  },
  {
    "answer": "kilobyte",
    "question": "What is often seen as the smallest unit of memory?"
  }
]

